- 얘들아, 나쁜 소식이 있어
- 뭔데?
-Hey. I got some bad news.
-What?
그래서 신문 팔겠냐, 이렇게 해 봐
"호외요, 호외! 모두 읽어보세요!"
That's no way to sell newspapers.
Try, "Extra! Extra! Read all about it!"
그게 아니라 모니카네 레스토랑이
포스트지 에서 악평을 받았어
No. Monica's restaurant got a horrible
review in the Post.
그래서 걔가 볼까봐 이 동네를
다 돌아서 모두 다 사버렸지
I didn't want her to see it, so I ran
around and bought all the copies.
둘, 넷, 여섯, 백만
그래, 다 사왔구나
Two, four, six, one million.
Yeah, you got them all.
이거 심한데
나도 악평을 받은 적이 있지
This is bad.
And I've had bad reviews.
그래도 내 첫 호평은 잊을 수 없어
I remember my first good one:
"우리 동네의 다른 모든 것은
형편없었는데"
"Everything else in Our Town
was terrible.
"조이 트리비아니는
구제 불능이었다"
Joey Tribbiani was abysmal."
우와! 저 신문들 좀 봐
Oh, my God!
Look at all the newspapers.
호평인가 보다, 아주 좋아?
It must be a good review. Is it great?
세상에!
Oh, dear God.
하지만 여기 두 블록 반경 내에
그걸 아는 사람은 없을 거야
But the good news is, no one
in a two-block radius will ever know.
- 그럼 나머지 맨해튼 사람들은?
- 모두 알겠지
-And the rest of Manhattan?
-They all know.
세상에, 이건 지독한데
정말 모욕적이야
Oh, my God, this is horrible.
I'm so humiliated.
악평이란 없다는 말도 있잖아
They say there's no such thing
as bad press.
"마히마히는 끔찍끔찍했다"
이게 악평이 아냐?
You don't think that "the mahi-mahi
was awful-awful" is bad press?
내가 쓴 거 아냐
I didn't write it.
- 사실이야? 내가 그렇게 형편없어?
- 아아니!
-God, is he right? Am I awful?
-Oh, no!
모니카, 내 말 들어봐
Monica, listen to me.
이건 내가 네 친구라서
하는 말이 아니라
I'm not just saying this
because I'm your friend.
네 요리는 구제 불능이야!
Your food is abysmal!
프렌즈 시즌 8
'모니카와 조이
요리학원에 가다'
- 로스?
- 뭐야? 뭐?
-Ross?
-What? What?
- 나 겁나 죽겠어!
- 그래?
-I am freaking out!
-Are you?
예정일이 이제 일주일 남았어!
My due date is in one week!
- 안 자고 뭐 해?
- 겨우 7일 남은 거야
-What are you doing up?
-That is seven days.
나 물 많이 마셨거든
우리 나중에...
I had a lot of water.
Can we do this after..?
아냐, 안돼 로스!
No, no, no, no, Ross!
필요한 물건들이 하나도 없잖아
We don't have any big stuff we need.
기저귀 갈아 채우는 테이블도 없고
아기 침대도 없고
We don't have a changing table or a crib.
- 기저귀 탁송 신청도 안했구
- 기저귀 얘기하니까 우습군
-We do not have a diaper service.
-Funny you should mention diapers.
- 나 심각해
- 걱정 마
-I'm serious.
-There's nothing to worry about.
웨스트 10번가에 아기 용품점이
있으니, 거기 가서
There's a baby store on West 10th.
We'll go there..
- 필요한 거 다 사자, 알았지?
- 알았어, 고마워
-and get everything we need. Okay?
-Okay. Thank you. That's great.
근데 웨스트 10번가 어딘데?
거기 신발 가게가 있는데...
Where on West 10th?
There's a shoe store..
알았어, 계속 얘기할 거면
나 화장실이나 갈래
Okay. If you're gonna do this,
then I'm gonna go do that, so..
- 잠깐만! 미안한데 하나만 더
- 뭔데
-Wait, Ross! I'm sorry, one more thing.
-Yeah.
우리 관계 말야, 우린 서로에게
어떤 의미인지
Our situation, you know,
what we mean to each other..
같이 애도 가졌고
함께 살고 있잖아
and, I mean, we're having this baby
together and we live together..
좀, 이상하지 않아?
Isn't that..? Isn't that weird?
글쎄...
Well..
농담이야, 가서 일이나 봐
I'm just kidding. You can go pee.
우리가 여기서 만나기로 했나
아니면 극장에서?
Did we say we were gonna meet here
or at the movie?
- 극장 앞에서
- 알았어, 거기서 보자
-We said at the movies, but..
-I'll see you there.
- 이왕 왔으니...
- 너 만나기 전까지 여기 있지 뭐
-Now that you're here..?
-I'll hang out till I have to meet you.
- 넌 왜 안 가?
- 오늘 면접 보거든
-How come you're not going?
-I've got a job interview.
- 일하고 있잖아
- 나한테 신경 많이 쓰는구나
-I thought you already have a job.
-And they say you don't pay attention.
더 좋은 자리야
회사의 부사장 자리거든
It's a better job.
It's vice president of the company..
다른 회사의 데이터를
재구성해주는 일이야
that does data reconfiguration
for other companies.
- 우와, 그런 건 언제 배웠어?
- 지금도 그 일 하잖아
-Wow. How do you know how to do that?
-That's what I do now.
- 조이, 와서 맛 좀 봐
- 뭔데?
-Joey? Come taste this.
-What?
나한테 악평 썼던
그 인간 기억 나지?
Remember the guy that gave me
a bad review? Well..
나 지금 복수하는 거야
I'm getting my revenge.
그 사람으로 요리했어?
You cooked him?
아니, 그 사람이
뉴스쿨에서 가르친대
No. He teaches a course
at The New School..
그 사람한테 내 부야베스를
다시 먹어보라고 할거야
I want to make him try
my bouillabaisse again.
내일 포스트지
제1면 기사가 기대 돼
I can't wait to read the front
page tomorrow:
"식당 비평가가 인정하기를
'모니카에 대한 내 의견은 틀렸다"'
"Restaurant reviewer admits:
'I was wrong about Monica.'"
제1면?
The front page?
넌 혼자만의 세상에서
살고 있구나?
You really do live in your own
little world, don't you?
- 나 영화 보러 가야겠다
- 아, 맞다
-I better get to my movie.
-Oh, yeah.
나도 영화 보러 가고
너도 영화 보러 간다면
If I'm going to the movie
and you're going to the movie..
우리 그냥 같이 가는 게
낫지 않나?
why don't we just go together?
내 데이터 재구성 능력이
어때, 챈들러?
How's that for data reconfiguration,
huh, Chand?
제 이름은 케이티예요
또 필요하신 거 있으세요?
My name's Katie if there's
anything else you need.
글쎄, 다 좋아 보여요
전부 다 사고 싶어요
Oh, God, I don't know. I want.. Everything
is so great, I just want everything.
이거 봐, 이거 필요해!
Oh, look at this. We need this!
- 이게 뭔데?
- 몰라
-What is it?
-I don't know.
왕관 안 쓴 사람들이
Have you ever had two people
who weren't wearing crowns..
이렇게 돈 많이 쓰는 거 봤어요?
spend this much money here?
좋은 걸 많이 고르셨어요
You have selected a lot of nice things.
이것들 배달해 드릴까요
겔러씨, 겔러 부인?
You want these delivered,
Mr. and Mrs. Geller?
- 어머, 아니에요
- 아니에요
-Oh, no, no.
-No, no.
- 우린 결혼 안 했어요
- 우리 아기를 곧 낳긴 하지만
-We're not married.
-We are having a baby..
서로 엮인 관계는 아니에요
but we're not involved.
무슨 말이냐면요
예전에 사귀었다가
I mean, we were seeing
each other a while ago..
그냥 친구로 지내다
어느날 밤 술이 취해서...
but then we were just friends, and
then there was one drunken night..
예, 처음보는 아가씨
이거 배달해주세요
Or, yes, stranger,
we'd like this delivered, please.
- 주소를 적어주시겠어요?
- 예
-Can you fill out this address card?
-Oh, okay.
- 공룡에 관한 걸 많이 고르셨네요
- 예
-You picked out a lot of dinosaurs.
-Yeah.
바로 그게 우리가 커플이
아닌 이유 중 하나예요
That's one of the reasons
why we're not a couple.
제가 골랐어요
전 고생물학자거든요
I chose those. I'm a paleontologist.
정말요? 근사해요
Really? That is so cool.
그렇게 흥분할 건 없어요
박사 같이 들리지만, 아니거든요
Don't get too worked up. It sounds
like he's a doctor, but he's not.
그게 아니라 전
고생물학에 관심 있어요
No. I'm fascinated by paleontology.
- 월터 알바레즈의 새 책 읽었어요?
- 제 수업 교재인걸요
-Have you read the Walter Alvarez book?
-I teach it in class.
카드 들고 계산대 앞에
서 있기 지루하네
Standing at a cash register, I'm
holding a credit card, and I'm bored.
제가 좋아하는 동네에 사시네요
근처에 좋은 헬스클럽이 있죠
I love your neighborhood.
There's a great gym around the corner.
- 저 거기 다녀요
- 운동 좀 하시는 것 같더라니까
-That's my gym.
-I could tell you work out.
운동하는 고생물학자라
인디애나 존스 같네요
A paleontologist who works out.
You're like Indiana Jones.
정말 인디애나 존스 같구나
I am like Indiana Jones.
- 안녕, 피비
- 안녕! 아기 물건 쇼핑은 어땠어?
-Hi, Pheebs.
-Hey! Oh, how did baby shopping go?
괜찮았어, 필요한 거 다 샀으니
Great! We got everything we needed.
아참, 로스는 목록에 없던
뭔가를 살 뻔 했지
Oh, and Ross almost got
something that wasn't on the list.
싸구려 계집애
A whore.
뭐?
What?
계산하려는데 판매 직원 여자가
로스한테 집적대는 거야
We were paying, and this sales
woman just started flirting with him.
기가 막히지?
Can you believe that?
- 부부 아닌 건 알고 있었어?
- 응
-Did she know you two weren't married?
-Yeah.
세상에, 여자가 총각한테
추근대다니
Oh, my God. Well, the idea..
A woman flirting with a single man?
- 교회 장로들한테 알려야겠다
- 그게 아냐
-We must alert the church elders.
-No.
네가 몰라서 그래
얼마나 뻔뻔스러웠는데
You don't understand.
You didn't see how brazen she was.
- 질투하는 것 같다
- 아니야
-Sounds like you're jealous.
-No, I'm not.
잘못된 것 같아서 그래
난 배가 뻥 터지기 직전인데
I just think it's wrong.
I mean, here I am, about to pop..
로스는 잡년 전문점에서 일하는
여자나 고르고 있으니
and he's out picking up
some shopgirl at Sluts-R-Us?
진짜 그런 데가 있어?
Is that a real place?
사람 안 뽑는대?
Are they hiring?
안녕, 피비, 배불뚝이
Hey, Phoebe. Fatty.
웬일로 쫙 빼 입었어?
Why so fancy?
면접 있거든
I got a job interview.
돈도 더 많이 주고
데이터 재구성하는 자리야
It's more money, and I'd be doing
data reconfiguration.
- 그런 일 하는 사람 아는데
- 나겠지, 내가 그 일 하잖아
-I think I know someone who does that.
-Me. I do that.
나 괜찮아 보여? 좀 긴장돼
So do I look okay?
I'm nervous.
그럼, 정말 멋지다
Oh, yeah. You look great.
그래도 너무 기대는 하지 마
You know, just don't
get your hopes up.
- 왜?
- 면접 말야
-Why not?
-Well, the interview.
- 그게 어쨌다구?
- 알잖아
-Yeah?
-You know.
너 첫인상 별로 안 좋은거
You don't make a very good
first impression.
- 뭐?
- 어머, 몰랐구나
-What?
-Oh, you don't know.
- 너 진담이야?
- 너 처음 봤을 때, 네가 너무...
-Are you serious?
-When I first met you, you were like:
그래서 내가
I was like:
뭐가 어땠는데?
What is it that I do?
그게, 너무 애 쓰는 것 같아
항상 농담하고
It's just, like, you're trying too hard,
making jokes..
좀 궁색하게 행동해
You come off a little needy.
너는 나 처음 만났을 때
마음에 들었어?
Did you like me when we first met?
챈들러, 거짓말은 안 할게
대신 도망갈거야
Chandler, I'm not gonna lie to you.
But I am gonna run away from you.
쟤 되게 뚱뚱해졌어
She's put on so much weight.
저기 있다
There he is.
저 잘난척 하는 자식
That smug bastard.
좋아요, 여러분
다음 시간에 봅시다
Okay, class.
We'll see you next time.
저 사람이구나
There he is.
안녕하세요, 모니카 겔러예요
알레산드로 요리사죠
Hi. I'm Monica Geller,
chef at Allessandro's.
아직도요?
Still?
저에 대한 평은
부당하다고 생각해요
The things you said were unfair..
그래서 제 부야베스를
다시 맛보셨으면 좋겠어요
and I want you to try
my bouillabaisse again.
나 자신에게 그럴 이유가
없다고 보는데요
I don't see why I'd do
that to myself again.
먹을거요? 쳐박힐거요?
Either eat it or be in it.
숟가락이요
Spoon?
- 어때요?
- 갈등 되네
-What do you think?
-I'm torn..
내 양심과 맞고 싶지는 않은
마음 가운데에서
between my integrity
and my desire to avoid a beating.
하지만 정직해야겠어요
당신 스프는 구제 불능이에요
But I must be honest.
Your soup is abysmal.
잘 됐다! 우리 이제 나가야 해
다른 수업이 시작되니까
Thattagirl! We should get out of here,
there's a new class coming in.
초보 요리 교실에
오신 걸 환영합니다
Welcome to lntroduction to Cooking.
홀랜데이즈와 버네이즈 소스의
차이점을 아시는 분?
Can anyone tell me the difference
between hollandaise and bearnaise sauce?
- 저요
- 말씀하세요
-I can.
-Okay, go ahead.
둘 다 달걀 노른자와 버터를
기본으로 하지만
Well, they both have a egg yolk
and butter base.
버네이즈는 샬롯, 차빌 그리고
제일 중요한 타라곤이 들어가요
But a bearnaise has shallots,
chervil, and most importantly, tarragon.
정말 잘했어요
이름이 뭐예요?
Very good. What's your name?
- 교실 맨 앞으로 가세요!
- 그럴게요!
-You go to the head of the class!
-Okay!
이 물건들이 자리를
많이 차지하네
This stuff takes up a lot of room.
벤이 네 인생에서 얼마나
중요한 자리를 차지하고 있어?
How serious are you about keeping
Ben in your life?
내 아들? 굉장히 중요하지
My son? Pretty serious.
어, 케이티, 무슨 일이에요?
Hi, Katie.
What are you doing here?
배달원이 나간 후
이게 빠진 걸 알았어요
The delivery went out
and they forgot this.
그 가게에 이거 하나밖에
안 남았을테니 찾기 쉬웠겠군요
It must have been obvious, since it
was the only thing left in your store.
저, 솔직히 말해서 배달은
제가 하는 일이 아니에요
Listen, to be honest, home deliveries
aren't really part of my job description.
실은 데이트 신청하려고 왔어요
Oh, I actually came here
to ask you out.
우와, 그거 괜찮은데요
Oh. Wow.
Yeah, that sounds great.
이건 다시 주머니에 넣고
없었던 일로 해요
I'm just gonna put this back in my
pocket and pretend that didn't happen.
지금 시간 있는데
커피나 같이 할까요?
I'm free now.
You want to get coffee..?
- 그래요
- 바람난 걸레 같으니
-Sure.
-Horny bitch.
아냐, 네가 바람난 걸레야!
No, you're a horny bitch!
가서 즐거운 시간 보내요
You guys have a good time.
난 가서 코트 가져올게요
내 채찍하고
I'm just gonna grab my coat.
And my whip.
인디애나 존스 같다면서요
You know, because of lndiana Jones.
제가 SM에 관심 있어서가
아니라요
Not because I'm into S & M.
전 이상한 것엔 관심 없어요
I'm not into anything weird, you know?
그냥 평범한 섹스만 해요
Just normal sex.
그럼 가서 코트나 가져올게요
So I'm gonna grab my coat.
오늘 좋은 날이었죠? 커미션도
많이 받고, 애 아빠도 하나 건지고
So you had a good day, huh?
Big commission, picked up a daddy.
저랑 로스가 이러는 거
당신 괜찮겠어요?
Are you okay with this?
아, 그럼요
로스랑 즐겁게 보내요
Oh, yeah. Yeah, please.
You guys have fun.
- 그럴게요
- 그래요
-Okay.
-Yeah.
만나서 반가웠어요
Nice to see you.
저도 만나서 반가웠어요
당신 정말 근사해 보여요
Oh, and it was great to see you too.
And you look fantastic.
- 단추 하나 떨어진 것만 빼구요
- 아, 실은 그게요...
-Although you missed a button.
-Oh, actually, I..
아하, 무슨 속셈인지 알겠네요
Oh, okay, I see
what you're doing there.
믿을 수 없어
내가 그렇게 행동한단 말야?
I can't even believe this.
I really come off that badly?
괜찮아, 좀 지나면
침착해지거든
It's okay. You calm down
after a while..
그러면 네가 얼마나
좋은 사람인지 알게 돼
and then people see
how wonderful you are.
그래, 그럼 면접을
몇 주 동안 봐야겠군
Good. Because I'm sure this
interview will last weeks.
너무 걱정하지 마
내가 도와줄게
All right, don't freak out, okay?
I will help you.
- 나가기 전까지 얼마나 남았니?
- 한 시간
-How long before you have to leave?
-An hour.
- 그럼, 못 도와주겠다
- 피비!
-I can't help you.
-Phoebe..
알았어, 최선을 다하자
난 면접관이고 널 처음 만나는 거야
We'll do our best. I'm the interviewer
and I'm meeting you for the first time.
- 알았어
- 반가워요, 레지나 팔렌지예요
-Okay.
-Hi. Come on in. I'm Regina Phalanges.
- 저는 챈들러 빙입니다
- 빙?
-Chandler Bing.
-Oh, Bing.
- 특이한 이름이네요
- 삼촌은 바다(badabing: 앗싸!)인걸요
-What an unusual name.
-You should meet my Uncle Bada.
제가 알아서 나갈게요
I'll let myself out.
알프레도가 좀 빡빡해 보이는데요
치즈 사용했어요?
Your alfredo's dry.
Did you use your cheese?
"사용"한다는 말이 요리 전
간식으로 먹는다는 뜻인가요?
When you say "use," do you mean
"eat as a pre-cooking snack"?
- 크림은요?
- 치즈는 목을 마르게 해요
-And the cream?
-Cheese makes me thirsty.
- 알았어요, 계속 해요
- 예
-Okay. Let's move on.
-All right.
모니카 작업대에서 맛있는
냄새가 나는데요
Something smells good
over at Monica's station.
우와! 놀라운 맛이네요
진짜 한번도 안 만들어봤어요?
My God! This is amazing!
You've never made this before?
전 요리에 대해서는
아무것도 몰라요
Oh, no. I don't know anything
about cooking.
물이 보글거리는게 뭔지
물어봐야 했는걸요
I had to ask what it was called when
the water makes those bubbles.
- 요리사 수준인데요
- 입에 잔뜩 들어서 못 들었어요
-Hats off to the chef.
-Your mouth was full. I didn't hear.
- 어떤 수준이요?
- 요리사요!
-Hats off to who?
-The chef!
바로 그거예요!
That's right!
저는 혼자서 관리를 하진 않습니다
서슴지 않고 위임할 것입니다
You'll find that I don't micromanage.
I don't shy away from delegating.
잘됐군요
하지 않을 일 말고
That's good to know. But let's stop
focusing on what you don't do..
할 일(do do, 똥)에 초점을
맞춰보죠
and focus on what you do do.
제가 할 일은
What I do do..
직원들이 서로 지지해주는
분위기를 만들어 내는 것입니다
is create an atmosphere of support
for the people working with me.
그렇군
똥 얘길 아주 잘 넘겼어
Nice sidestep on the "do do" thing.
- 너무 힘들었어
- 어머, 너 이제 가야 해!
-Hardest thing I've ever done.
-Oh, you gotta go!
- 걱정 마, 잘 할거야
- 정말?
-Don't worry. You're ready.
-Really?
물론이지, 너의 자연 본능만
이겨내면, 문제없어
Absolutely! Just fight all your
natural instincts, and you'll be great.
모니카, 이거 봐
Monica, check these out.
쿠키 같은데
Those look like cookies.
그래, 내가 다 만든 거야
I know, yeah.
And I made them all by myself.
재료를 섞어서 오븐에
넣었다 꺼냈지
I mixed the ingredients,
I put them in the oven, I took them out.
오븐용 장갑 끼는 걸
잊었지만, 어쨌든
Granted, I should have used
the oven mitts, but still.
모니카, 우리 스타 학생
Monica, my star student.
아까 그렇게 불러서 말인데요
알루미늄 포일로 별을 만들었어요
You called me that before,
so I fashioned a star out of foil.
부담 갖지 말고 제 쿠키가
맛있으면 별을 주세요
Now, no pressure. If you like my
cookies, you give me the star.
우와, 별이다!
Wow, a star!
다들 날 싫어하는 건 알아요
미안하지만, 난 상관 안 해요
I know you all hate me,
and I'm sorry, but I don't care.
- 조이, 당신 차례예요
- 네
-Okay, Joey, you're up next.
-Yeah.
와! 훌륭한데요!
Oh, my God! This is amazing!
A를 줄게요
You get an A.
제가 A를요? 그것도 학교에서?
나 범생이 됐네!
I got an A? In school?
Hey, I'm a dork!
네가 자랑스럽다, 조이
Joey, I'm so proud of you.
- 그 별, 조이에게 줘야겠는데요
- 뭐라구요?
-I think you should give him your star.
-Excuse me?
- 쟤는 요리에 '요'자도 몰라요
- 우리 모두 다 마찬가지예요
-He doesn't know what he's doing.
-Nobody knows what they're doing.
전 알아요
저는 전문 요리사라구요
I do. I'm a professional chef!
됐어요, 무슨 법정 드라마
찍어요?
Oh, relax. It's not a courtroom drama.
진짜 전문 요리사라면
초보 요리 교실에 왜 왔어요?
Why are you taking
Introduction to Cooking?
그러게!
Yeah!
미안해요
전 알레산드로 주방장인데
I'm sorry. I cook at this restaurant,
Allessandro's..
악평을 받았거든요
and I just got a bad review.
- 알레산드로? 나 거기 좋아해요!
- 그래요?
-Allessandro's? I love that place!
-You do?
당신은 훌륭한 요리사예요
근데 인간적으로는 좀...
You're a great chef.
As a person you're a little..
- 완전히 미쳤죠, 제 음식은 좋아해요?
- 정말 좋아해요
-Oh, I'm crazy, but you liked the food?
-Very much.
그럼, 난 형편없지 않아
난 훌륭한 요리사예요!
Okay, then. I don't stink.
I'm a good chef! Okay.
난 가기 싫어, 재밌단 말야
I don't want to go. I'm having fun.
근데 당신들 수업료는 냈어요?
Did either of you pay for this class?
이봐요, 내 친구가
가자면 가는 거예요!
Hey, if my friend says
it's time to go, it's time to go!
저희 회사에서 KL-5을 GR-6로
바꾸는 일을 했었습니다
I was the point person on my company's
transition from the KL5 to GR6 systems.
- 매우 바빴겠군요
- 맞아요, 그랬습니다
-You must have had your hands full.
-That I did. That I did.
그럼 이제 당신 일(doodie, 똥)에
대해 얘기하죠
So let's talk a little bit
about your duties.
제 일이요?
My duties?
그러죠
All right.
부서 전체를 맡아야 하니까
일이 많을 거예요
You'll be heading a whole division,
so you'll have a lot of duties.
- 그렇군요
- 당신 밑으로 30명 정도 되니깐
-I see.
-But there'll be 30 people under you..
그들에게 좀 퍼주어도 돼요
so you can dump
a certain amount on them.
- 다행이군요
- 더 자세히 얘기하자면...
-Good to know.
-We could go into detail..
아뇨, 안 하셔도 됩니다
No, don't, I beg of you.
좋습니다, 확답은
월요일에 드리겠지만
All right. We'll have a definite
answer for you on Monday.
당신이 여기에 잘 맞을 거라는
확신이 서는군요
But I can say with some
confidence, you'll fit in well here.
- 정말입니까?
- 물론이죠
-Really?
-Absolutely.
- 이젠 긴장 풀어요, 잘했습니다
- 감사합니다
-You can relax. You did great.
-Yeah, thanks.
긴장을 많이 했어요, 농담이
지나치다는 말을 들어서요
I was really nervous.
I'm told I come on too strongly.
그 "일"에 관한 건
진짜 넘기기 힘들었어요
And then it was really hard
to sidestep that "duty" thing.
일?
Duties?
똥이요
Doodies?
응가 말이에요
Poo?
응가?
이건 상관없는 거죠?
면접은 끝났으니까요
Oh, my God. This doesn't count. Okay?
The interview was over.
저기 있던게 진짜 챈들러 빙이고
여기 있는 건 미친놈이에요
That was the real Chandler Bing.
This is some crazy guy.
경비 불러요!
복도에 미친 놈이 있어요!
Call security! There's a crazy guy
out in the hall!
응가 라고?
Poo?
그럼 전화 기다리겠습니다
I'll look forward to your call.
- 나 왔어
- 안녕
-Hey.
- 왔구나
- 어때?
-You're back.
-How are you?
좋아, 그건 중요한게 아냐
중요한 건 그 여자 어땠냐는 거지
I'm fine. But that's not important.
What's important is how was she?
재밌었어, 그냥 커피 마셨어
It was fun.
We just had coffee.
수다 떨고 커피 마시면서
테이블 밑으로 더듬는 거?
Oh, uh-huh, uh-huh, coffee,
a little rub-rub-rub under the table?
왜 그래? 케이티가 싫어?
What's going on?
Do you not like Katie?
아니, 그 여자 괜찮더라
좀 헤프지만, 누군들 안 그런가?
No. No, she was nice. I mean,
she was a little slutty, but who isn't?
난 좋던걸
Well, I liked her.
당연하지, 넌 인디애나 존스라고
불러주면 고릴라도 데이트 할걸
Of course you did. You'd date a gorilla
if it called you lndiana Jones.
오늘 임신 호르몬이
한 바가지 새로 생겼어?
Did you get a fresh batch
of pregnancy hormones today?
아냐, 그냥
케이티 때문에 신경 쓰여
No. It's just that..
Katie bothered me.
왜? 그 여자 어디가 문제야?
Why? What was wrong with her?
문제 하나도 없어
사랑스러운 여자야
There was nothing wrong with her.
She was lovely.
- 그럼 뭐가 문제야?
- 그 여자랑 데이트 하는게 싫어
-Okay. So, what's the matter?
-I don't want you to date her.
왜? 질투하는 거야?
Why? What, are you jealous?
응, 나랑 데이트 하길
바라는 건 아니지만
Yes. And not because
I want you to go out with me.
네가 누구랑
데이트 하는 것도 싫어
Because I don't want you
to go out with anybody.
이게 지독하다는 것도 알고
타당하지 않은 것도 알지만
It's terrible to even think this
and it's inappropriate..
난 네가 내 옆에서 하루 24시간
대기했으면 좋겠어
but I want you to be at my constant
beck and call, 24 hours a day.
정말 미안하지만
지금 내 심정이 그래
I'm very sorry, but that is
just the way that I feel.
- 알았어
- 뭐?
-Okay.
-What?
데이트 안 할게
I won't date. I'll..
네 옆에 항상 있어 줄게
I'll be here with you all the time.
정말?
Really?
말도 안 되는 소리인데도?
But I'm being so unreasonable.
그렇긴 하지만 그럴 자격이 있어
우리 아기를 가졌잖아
True, but you're allowed to be
unreasonable. You're having our baby.
로스, 고마워
정말 고마워
Oh, Ross, thank you. Thank you.
좀 괜찮아졌어?
You feel better?
아니, 네가 내 방광 쪽으로
아기를 눌러서
No, not really. You're pressing
the baby into my bladder..
화장실 가고 싶어졌어
and now I have to pee.
- 어휴
- 레이첼?
-Okay.
-Rach?
- 응?
- 있잖아
-Yeah?
-Just one thing..
우린 같이 살고 아기도 가졌고
난 아무와도 데이트 하지 않을텐데
We live together. You're having our
baby. I'm not gonna see anybody else.
다른 건 원하는 거 없어?
Are you sure you don't want
something more?
흐음, 글쎄...
Wow. I don't know, maybe..
레이첼, 나 그냥 장난친거야
Oh, Rach, I was just messing around.
- 너도 나 화장실 갈 때 그랬잖아
- 이런! 그럴 줄 알았어
-Like you did when I had to pee?
-Oh! I knew that.
그럴 줄 알았어, 나도 장난친거야!
I knew that!
I was just messing with you too!
알았어, 근데 순간 네가...
Okay. Because for a minute
you seemed..
- 아냐, 그냥...
- 꼭 네가 정말로...
-No, it's just..
-Like you actually..
나 장난치는 데 소질 있거든!
That's just because I'm such
a good messer!
- 레이첼?
- 응?
-Rach?
-Yeah?
- 화장실 안 가?
- 맞다
-The bathroom?
-Right.
진짜 재밌었어, 요리도 배우고
맛있는 것도 먹고
I had a great time. I learned how to bake,
ate great food.
중1 때 이후 처음으로 A도 받고
이번엔 선생이란 잠도 안 잤는데
It's my first A since 7th grade and
I didn't even sleep with the teacher.
- 여기 봐, 초보 연기 교실이야
- 그러네
-Oh, look. Acting for Beginners.
-Yeah.
- 더 기분 좋아지고 싶니?
- 그러지 뭐!
-Wanna feel good about yourself?
-What the hell!
기본적인 것부터 시작하겠습니다
Let's start with some basics.
업스테이지와 다운스테이지의
차이점을 아는 사람 있나요?
Can anybody tell me what the difference
between upstage and downstage is?
이건 바보 같은 생각이었어
Yeah, this was a stupid idea.